pcnation.com 2011-12-11

# Security & Privacy Policy - Buy with confidence | PCNation.com

---  
  
|    |  |   
---|---|---  

|  | 

  * ### Privacy

At PCNation.com, we respect your right to privacy. You can rest assured that PCNation does not sell or share ANY of your personal information with anyone outside of PCNation. The information we gather is only used for enhancing the functionality and content of our site. As a PCNation Customer, you'll occasionally receive e-mail updates about important functionality changes to our web site, new PCNation services, and special offers we believe would be beneficial to you. We hope you'll find these updates interesting and informative. If you'd rather not receive them, you can unsubscribe at any time by following the unsubscribe procedure described in the e-mail. 

  * ### Cookies

What is a cookie? A cookie is a tiny bit of text used by a browser to store information. Cookies cannot profile your system or collect information from your hard drive. Almost every web site that offers online ordering or customized content utilizes cookies. Although you may receive cookies from many different sites, each cookie can only be read by the web server that originally issued it. PCNation.com uses cookies when a customer chooses to create a shopping cart. Our cookie ONLY contains information regarding the items you have placed in your shopping cart such as part numbers and prices. We do not use cookies to store credit card numbers, address information or any other personal information. 

  * ### Security

PCNation wants to make your on-line shopping easy, secure and worry-free. To safeguard all your shopping transactions we employ the latest security methods in protecting your personal information. This includes a Verisign Secure Server Certificate to encrypt your credit card and personal information during a purchase. PCNation employs the Internet's Secure Socket Layer ("SSL") security technology. If you access the Internet with a recent version of Microsoft Internet Explorer, Chrome, Safari and Opera your browser supports SSL. When you begin the checkout procedure your browser will automatically be directed to our secure commerce server so that all your personal information will be encrypted before it is transmitted over the Internet. 

|   
---|---|---  
  
Copyright © 1996-2011 PCNation. All rights reserved.
